(Episode 92) I have made a decision.
I'm taking my mom
abroad for treatment.
Okay,
I will have Michael
contact that doctor.
I just don't know
how long it will take
to come back.
I will make arrangements
for everything.
Just take your mom there.
You don't need to worry about the rest.
Besides my mom's surgery,
I'm not worried about anything else.
I'll deal with
your father's things.
At least before you return,
I can make sure
he won't cause you any problems.
I
still worry...
What are you worried about?
Worried about me?
This way,
you won't have to worry anymore, right?
What are you doing?
I promised you
that I would put a real ring
on your finger.
You
remembered all that?
I'm sorry.
After we separated,
I went back to Elveron,
and then I got seriously ill.
I forgot everything
between us
and have developed
insomnia since then.
I know you've been waiting for me.
Now I'm ready,
I'm ready to spend the rest of my life
to make it up to you.
So, Noemi,
are you willing to
grant my wish?